差不多11点了
it's almost 11:00.
她需要多睡
She needs a lot of sleep these days.
求你, Bardach夫人
Please,mrs. Bardach.
我好几星期没见她了
I haven't seen her for a week.
我知道她的感觉
I'll see how she's feeling.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道怎么做
You know what to do.
好了?
all done?
我搓了45秒, 刷了指甲
I,scrubbed for 45 seconds,did the nails,
一直洗到手肘
all the way down the elbows,the whole deal.
你病了?
Are you sick?
没有没有
No,no,no.
咳嗽 喉咙痛?
Cough,sore throat?
没有 我看见强光就会打喷嚏
No,no.I just--sometimes I sneeze when I look at lights.
一直都是
I always have.
对不起 你还是--
I'm sorry. You better--
我不会让她生病的
I would never get her sick.
求你了
Please.
口罩
A mask.
被看门的抓住了
Got me by the bouncer.
她疯了
She's crazy.
过去两个月我只出去过6次
She's let me out like six times in the last two months.
每次只是去医院,我是犯人
Every time it's just to go to the hospital.I'm a prisoner.
会好的
Aw,it's okay.
真丑
It's ugly.
不对
No.
再说我看的也不是那里
I wasn't looking at the scar anyways.
摘掉口罩
Take off your mask.
如果你妈进来--
if your mom comes in here,she--
吻我, 否则我杀了你
hey,give me a kiss or I'll kill you.
你的皮肤, 你怎么了?
Your skin.Are you okay?
Melinda, 你怎么--
Melinda,can you--
出什么事了, 你能呼吸吗?
what's wrong? What's wrong?Can you breathe?
怎么了, 是心脏吗?
What's wrong?Is it your heart?
怎么了?
What's wrong?
Bardach太太!
Mrs. Bardach! Miss--
melinda, 我不知道怎么用,我从来没用过
melinda,I don't know how to use this.I've neversed one of these before.
你对她做了什么?
What did you do to her?
cuddy打过电话
cuddy called.
知道, 我看来电显示了
I know. Saw the caller id.
年轻女孩, 过敏症
Young girl,anaphylactic shock.
你接了?
You answered?
原来, 接起电话才能让铃声停止
Turns out that's what stops the ringing.
很古怪的病例
It's a weird case.
我以为你昨晚洗了盘子,该你值日
I Thought you did the dishes last night.It was your day.
我洗了, 这些是新的,宵夜
I did. Those are new.Midnight snack.
为了宵夜,  你做了炖肉
For a midnight snack,you made a pot roast.
和我昨晚做的炖肉一样
The same pot roast i made last night.
实际上是半夜以后
Actually,it was after midnight.
今天轮到你,  对吧?
Today is your day,right?
我想让我走, 我懂
You want me out of here.I get it.
不 你可以留在这里
No,it's fine if you stay.
我会搬去别处,那人还没打给我
The place I was gonna move, the guy never called.
我说了, 你留在这里没问题
I said it's fine if you stay.
这就是我的可悲之处
That's why you're making me miserable.
也许我只是想让你做好你的值日
Maybe I just want to make sure you do your fair share around here.
那个--
Tha--
有什么不妥?
what's weird about it?
过敏的那个女孩
The girl with the allergies.
她的免疫系统被破坏了
She's immunocompromised.
你这是怎么了?
What are you doing?
怎么了? 不是你问我的--
What? You asked me--
你知道我很感兴趣
you knew that I was interested.
这可是你的筹码
That gives you a valuable bargaining chip.
你可以逼我洗一周的盘子
You could've had me doing dishes for a week.
好吧
Okay.
发生过敏反应时,她在一个洁净的房间
The allergic reaction happened while she was in a clean room.
她家里怎么会有超净室?
Why does she have a clean room in her home?
心脏移植, 免疫系统被抑制了
Heart transplant.Immune system's in the toilet.
妈妈给她造了个,john travolta级别的泡泡
Mommy builds her little angel a john travolta-quality bubble.
术后6个月,  其实不必待在超净室了
Six months after the transplant,she doesn't need to be confined to a clean room.
6个月没有男人
Six months without putting out,
Cuddy医生完全不必穿丁字裤,但这不归我们管
dr. Cuddy doesn't need to wear thong panties,but it's not our call.
你什么时候知道我的内裤了?
I was wondering when you'd get around to my panties.
她已经做了4天的检查
She's had four days of workups.
他们测试了所有能进房间的人,里面所有的物品
They've tested everyone who came anywhere near that room,everything in the room.
简直是克里斯丁式的悬疑
It's like an agatha christie mystery.
也许不是因为什么东西,是她做了什么
Maybe it's not what was there.It's what she was doing.
行为过敏, 我喜欢
Exercise allergy.Love it.
青春期的少男少女在一起能做什么呢?
What sort of exercise could a strapping young man and a nubile teenage nymphet possibly--
妈妈很快就进屋了
mom was in the room within seconds.
这么说男孩带来了致敏原,并且撒谎隐瞒
So the boyfriend brought in an allergen and is lying about it.
或者是女孩子溜出去,并且撒谎隐瞒
Or the girl snuck out and she's lying about that.
或者父母对房间的洁净程度撒谎了
Or the parents are lying about the room being clean.
这就是你们的分析?,有人在撒谎?
These are your big ideas?Somebody's lying?
从未失手过
Hasn't let me down yet.
再次检查妈妈爸爸女孩男孩房间和整栋房
Recheck mom,dad,the girl,the boy,the room,and the home.
谁用了新的香皂, 洗涤剂, 香水?
Any of you have a new soap,detergent,perfume?
没有, Barbara对这些方面很当心
No. Barbara's really careful about that stuff.
你最近没出去过?
And you haven't been outside recently?
怎么出去? 我被关在那里
How could I?I'm trapped up there.
不是关你, 只是保证安全--
You're not trapped.It's just safe--
报警器密码都不告诉我
they won't even tell me the alarm code.
告诉她我可以回学校
Just tell her I can go back to school.
查清楚就可以
Till we clear this up.
行, 查出我对什么过敏,我小心点就是了
Fine.Find out what I'm allergic to,and I'll stay away from it.
然后我就能回学校了, 对不对?
Then I can go back to school,right?
这由你父母决定
It's up to your parents.
- 从医学角度上讲, 没有理由-,- 告诉过你
But medically,there's no reason--told you.
能不能到外面说句话?
Could I speak to you outside for a second,please?
我希望你不要给出--
You know,this is hard enough without you in there giving--
她在向我咨询
she asked my opinion.
她16岁, 不用对她说真话
She is 16 years old.Lie to her.
我8岁的时候 我母亲--
When I was eight,my mom,she hated--
我知道, 我得放开点,我保护过度了
I know.I-I need to loosen up.I'm overprotective.
我看过海底总动员,我不需要大道理
I saw finding nemo.I get it.I don't need another story.
你可不是过度保护
But you're not just being overprotected.
你是我见过的最过度保护的父母
You're one of the most overprotective parents i've ever seen.
我给她最好的家庭教师
She has the best private tutors.
我让她的朋友探访,我问心无愧
I let her friends visit.I'm not going to apologize.
只是告诉你我的想法
Just giving you my thoughts.
她小时候三次差点没命
She almost died three times during her childhood.
青霉素, 蜜蜂, 花生
Penicillin,bee stings,peanuts.
我看过她的病例
I've seen her file.
6个月前,我们第一次离开她去渡周末
Six month ago,we leave her home alone for the first time on a weekend.
她出去了, 买了巧克力饼干,带花生酱的
She goes out,buys one chocolate chip cookie.Peanut butter in the dough.
她没带急救针, 开车去的医院,中途昏倒, 出了车祸
She's forgotten her epi pen,she drives to the hospital,passes out,has an accident.
方向盘压碎了她的胸腔,她失去了心脏
Steering wheel crushed her chest.She ended up losing her heart.
你要跟我说
So when you say to me
我是最过度保护的家长之一, 请你...
that I'm one of the most overprotective parents you've seen,please...
请你介绍更过度保护的家长给我认识
please introduce me to the ones who were more protective
我看看我哪里做的还不够好
so that I can find out what they're doing right.
也许她对郁闷的社交生活过敏
Maybe she's allergic to having a sucky social life.
别指责她的家长了,他们是在保护她的健康
Give the parents a break.They're just trying to keep her healthy.
这里的所有东西都写着"绝不致敏",不过还是查一下吧
Everything in here's labeled "hypoallergenic."  Check it anyway.
Cameron.
这地方比医院还干净
This place is cleaner than her hospital room.
这扇窗户没报警器
No alarm on this window.
这里高20英尺
It's 20-foot drop.
可以从这里到树上,这里的树皮刮掉了
You can get to the tree from here.There's some bark scraped off.
是啊, 心脏移植的女孩,挂在藤条上荡
Sure. Heart-transplant girl swung wn there on a vine.
也许她和人猿泰山有一腿
Maybe she was hooking up with tarzan
然后骑着猎豹直奔大象墓园
and cheetah down by the elephant graveyard.
或者...女主角留在树屋里,泰山上来
Or...jane stayed in the tree house and tarzan came up.
好吧, 周五晚上我逗留很长时间
Okay.I spent most of the night friday.
被她妈妈知道的话,会发疯的
But if her mom finds out about that,she will totally freak.
你们做爱了?
You guys had sex?
可是我已经采取措施,不让她得病
But,you know,I did everything I could to make sure she wouldn't get sick.
乳胶过敏?
A latex allergy?
什么意思? 避孕套?,我们没有
What do you mean,like a condom? We didn't--
你们没有做防护?,你对不安全性爱一无所知吗?
you had unsafe sex?The whole unsafe thing didn't tell you something?
做了, 可我们并不是计划好的
Yeah,but we didn't like plan on it,you know?
只不过..,我们深深相爱,我们一起已经两年
It just--I don't know.We're in love.We've been dating for two years.
相当长的时间了,会不会是精液过敏?
Practically a lifetime.How about a semen allergy?
我们需要精液样本
We're gonna need a semen sample.
你可以到那边的洗手间
You can use the bathroom over there.
知道了, 我怎么...
Right. how do I...
瞄准了就射
aim and shoot.
不准幻想Cameron,我们会知道的
No thinking about dr. Cameron.We'll know.
我们应该告诉家长
We should tell her parents.
就这样? 索性报警好了
Why stop there?Call the cops.
Melinda还未成年
Melinda's a minor.
如果我们说出去,这俩孩子可能再也不能有性爱
And if we nip it in the bud here,teenagers will never again have sex.
反正家长拿到帐单的时候会发现
The parents will find out when they get the bill anyway.
所以他们自己发现就无所谓
Oh,so you're fine with them finding out
只要不让你去告诉他们?
as long as you don't have to tell them personally?
差不多
Pretty much.
可惜不是取你的样本,否则现在都已经搞定了
Too bad it's not you giving the sample.We'd be done by now.
测试呈阴性,没有精液过敏
Test was negative.No semen allergy.
男朋友在前一晚溜进去和她温存
Boyfriend sneaks in to get his freak on the night before the anaphylaxis.
我不信这没有关联
I don't buy that it's unrelated.
他爱她, 他做了一切措施,防止她生病
He loves her.Did everything he could to make sure she wouldn't get sick.
这说明什么?
What does that mean?
只有部分人能感受到爱这种体验,快乐也是如此
Love is an emotion certain people experience,similar to happiness.
算了 我还是找点更贴切的例子
No. Maybe I should give a more relatable example.
行了!
Oh,snap!
他采取了什么措施保护她?
What did he do to protect her?
用猪鬃刷清洗私处?
Brillo-pad his privates?
假设他洗了, 而且--
I assumed he washed and he--
很好, 假设比问题要快速
oh,good work.Assumptions are so much faster than actual questions.
你是男朋友?,跟我来一下
You the boyfriend?Need to borrow you.
怎么了?
What is going on?
别担心, 我会把他大致原样送回
Don't worry. I'll return him in roughly the same condition.
你服用什么来保持健康?
Do you take anything to stay healthy?
不是指每天一个苹果的?
Something stronger than an apple a day?
他没事吧?
Is he okay?
他累了...因为昏迷太久
He's just tired...from being in a coma so long.
你吃了什么?
What'd you take?
别担心, 他会保守秘密
Don't worry.He can keep a secret.
抗生素?青霉素?
Antibiotics?Penicillin?
有没有比较熟的?
Any of those names ring a bell?
我朋友elliot, 他爸爸开了一瓶没吃完
my friend elliot,his dad had,like,a whole bottle that he hadn't finished,
我就拿过来,吃了大概一星期
so I swiped it and took a bunch for,like,a week.
我不会冒险把病菌传染给melinda
There's no way I was gonna risk breathing germs on melinda.
青少年性爱就是这么麻烦,你个白痴
This is the one downside of teenage sex:You're idiots.
你差点杀死你的女友
You almost killed your girlfriend.
她对青霉素过敏
She's allergic to penicillin.
你是说我嘴唇上还有?,我刷了牙的
What,do you think there was still some on my lips?I brushed my teeth.
位置再靠下点,有趣的地方
Think lower and more fun.
那能从...从那东西里穿过去?
I mean,it can--it can go through your stuff?
绝无问题
Totally,dude.
这医院有个行政管理,每次她一生病
There's this administrator here,whenever she gets sick,
就让我吃方子上的药
she just gives me the prescription.
可是他们做了测试,说melinda不会对我的那东西过敏
But you know,they tested melinda,they said.she wasn't allergic to my stuff.
四天了
Yeah,four days later.
那些青霉素早都在你洗衣蓝底部,的臧袜子上结痂了
By that time,the penicillin was crusting up a sock at the bottom of your hamper.
你一定会告诉她是我的错吗?
Do you have to tell her it was my fault?
不
No.
做成年人的好处,没什么一定要做的
Great part of being a grownup,you never have to do anything.
你们让她出院?
You're releasing her?
怎么回事? 你们发现什么?
What happened?What did you find out?
对你家的检查排除了环境致敏
Tests on your house ruled out any environmental allergens.
好, 那到底是什么?
Yeah,but what caused this?
我们相信这种情形不太可能再出现
We believe it's highly unlikely that this set of circumstances will repeat itself.
什么情形?
What set of circumstances?
这是好消息 表示她健康
It's good news.She's healthy.
- 但我觉得你应该找- ,- cameron!
But you might want to talk-- --cameron!
我不能呼吸
I can't breathe.
肾上腺素
Getting the epi.
给她打针
give her the shot!
心音正常, 没有摩擦声
No murmurs,no friction rubs.
你们等什么?
What are you waiting for?
安静
Quiet.
她咳白沫
She's coughing up white sputum.
上行三分之二有气泡声
Crackling two-thirds of the way up.
看她的脖子
Look at her neck.
她在呕吐, 你们还不打针?
She is vomiting.Would you give her the shot?
不是过敏, 是她的心脏
It's not an allergy.It's her heart.
好消息是什么?坏消息是什么?
what's the good news?What's the bad news?
充血性心衰
Congestive heart failure.
好还是坏?
Is which?
好消息
Good news.
为什么?
Why?
不知道, 这样比较像你
I don't know.It just sounded like you.
新的拼图, 总是好的,坏消息是什么?
New puzzle piece.Always good news.What's the bad news?
两个碎片来自不同的拼图
We've got two puzzle pieces from two different puzzles.
有道理
Seems that way.
假如过敏症不是过敏症?
What if her anaphylaxis wasn't anaphylaxis?
抗排异药物可导致痉挛和心衰
Toxicity from the anti-rejection meds could cause a seizure and then heart failure.
结果被妈妈手里的肾上腺素治好?,这就是过敏, 还有什么?
And get cured by a mommy-wielded epi pen?It's anaphylaxis.What else?
假如确实是两个拼图呢?
What if they really are two puzzles?
她在一周内连中两个疑难杂症?
You think she had two unrelated rare conditions in one week?
我们解释了过敏
We explained the anaphylaxis.
什么, 我们? 是我
What do you mean,we?I did!
至少我认为是,结果还是我的功劳
At least I thought I did.Maybe I didn'T.Still,it was all me.
心脏的问题, 对一个心移植患者来说,并不少见
Heart problems aren't so rare for someone who's had a heart transplant.
我们假设house对过敏的判断是对的
I say we assume house was right about the anaphylaxis.
很诱人
It is tempting.
心脏衰竭可以有几种原因,感染, 冠状动脉疾病, 排异
Heart failure could be either infection,coronary disease,or rejection.
我们把它叫白板是有原因的,不是我规定的
Sorry. There's a reason they call it the white board.It's not my rule.
这些病因如何联系在一起?
What ties both these conditions together?
我们可以面面相觑
Okay,we can all stare at each other,
或者我们调查心衰的原因
or we can investigate what caused the heart failure.
只是心衰
Just the heart failure.
把马克笔给我好吗?
You wanna give me that black marker?
没有发烧, 应该没有感染
There's no fever,so it's probably not infection.
或者, 没有发烧是因为过去6个月,她的免疫系统一直被抑制
or no fever because she's been on immunosuppressants for the last six months.
我们做个C.T, 心脏活检,重新验血
let's do a C.T.,Get a heart biopsy and redo the blood work.
发现什么?
Anything?
还没有
Not yet.
听说你不赞同青少年性爱
So I hear you don't want teenagers having sex.
青少年自杀率还不够高吗?
Teen suicide rate isn't high enough for you already?
我只是觉得这两个人被宠坏了
I just think those two are brats.
女儿一有机会就给她妈捣乱
The girl undercuts her mother any chance she gets.
女儿的错,妈妈拿她当小孩就没什么
It's the daughter's fault.Has nothing to do with mom infantilizing her.
好理由
Good point.
解释了为什么不关心小孩的家长
Explains why parents who don't pay attention
总是养出懂事的好孩子
get such nice,well-adjusted children.
这是什么?
What's this?
可能是赘生物?
Think it's vegetation?
好像是拉动心脏瓣膜的肌肉
The kind made of muscle that opens your heart valves.
没事, 她很正常
It's nothing.She's clean.
好消息 你没有任何心血管疾病
it's good news.You don't show any signs of coronary artery disease.
接下来是什么?
So what's next?
血检以排除感染
Well,blood work to rule out infection,
心外科活检以排除排异反应
and then a heart surgical biopsy to rule out rejection.
但是你觉得不可能两个都排除?
But you don't think you're gonna rule out both things,do you?
是的
No.
我会失去这个心脏, 是么?
I'm gonna lose this heart,right?
希望我们找到原因, 治好它
Hopefully we'll find the problem and fix it.
你的心还可以用很久
You'll keep your heart a long time.
多久?
How long?
医学的进步可以让你的心用几十年
There could be drug breakthroughs that allow you to keep it for decades more.
我的心脏科医生也是这么说的
That's the answer my cardiologist always gives me.
我在网上查过
I looked it up on the web.
差不多5年10年, 不是吗?
It's like five or ten years,right?
那是个平均数
That's about the average.
所以我需要生活
That's why I need to have a life.
为什么你不说服我妈让我回学校?
Why can't you convince my mom to let me go back to school?
Melinda,你现在的情况比失学更紧要
Melinda,you've got bigger worries right now than missing school.
我们查处你的心脏出了什么问题之前
Until we figure out what's wrong with your heart,
最安全的地方是家里
the safest place for you to be is right here.
那个...妓女在哪里?
where'S...the hooker,I assume?
在我这里, 兄弟
Right up here,buddy.
你说把听诊器挂上表示你在享受性爱
You said you'd hang the stethoscope if you were having sex.
我没说一定和人
I didn't say it had to be with another person.
你能不能想出任何
Can you think of anything that
把过敏和心衰联系起来的因素?
would tie together anaphylaxis and heart failure?
没有
No.
我在外面等了几个小时!
I was waiting out there for hours!
我这人前戏很长
I need a lot of foreplay.
结束后还要爱抚
And then there's the cuddling afterwards.
有无可能不是过敏症,但还是对肾上腺素有反应?
Any way that anaphylaxis isn't anaphylaxis even it responds to epi?
没有,难怪你这么有兴致
No. no wonder you were in the mood.
本月的心脏学期刊
This month's new jersey journal of cardiology.
你看了中间彩页了?
Have you seen the centerfold?
那些瓣膜不可能是真的
There's no way those valves are real.
有无可能心功能衰竭是因为--
Any chance that the heart failure could be unrelated to--
不, 如果你工作时不想被打扰,你可以说出来
no.If you need time alone to work,you just have to say so.
你不必说谎
You don't have to lie about it.
骗人好玩
Lying's more fun.
被骗就没那么好玩
Being lied to,not as much fun.
请给出一个答案:
Please have an answer to this question:
晚餐吃什么?
What's for dinner?
还是没刷盘子?
You still haven't done the dishes?
要不要来点?,好像还有几个蓝莓
You want one of these?I think I got a couple of blueberries.
不好意思, 只有一个
Nope. Sorry. Just one.
别这么沮丧
Oh,don't look all weepy.
对我有意见, 冲我来啊
You got a problem with me,deal with it.
剪我的床单之类的
Short my sheets or something.
活检排除了排异反应
biopsy was negative for rejection.
感谢上帝
Thank god.
血检的结果?
And what about the blood tests?
没有感染
Showed no infection.
所以我们还是不知道心衰的原因
So we still don't know what caused her heart failure.
我们可以暂时高兴一下,她不需要另一个心脏
Let's just be happy she doesn't need a new heart.
Bardach太太, 这可能只是一次偶然
Mrs. Bardach,it could have just been a one-time thing.
她有过敏反应和心力衰竭
So she has an allergic reaction and heart failure,
两样都没有眉目
and neither of them can be explained.
你们还在做什么检测?
Are they doing any more tests on her?
- 没有,- 她不在这里
No.She's not here.
通知本地医院, 出租车公司,州警和本地警局
notify local hospitals,cab companies,the state troopers,and local cops.
休班安全人员取消休假
Any security officers off duty are back on duty.
马上办理
we're on it.
我需要一些照片,检查那几个抽屉
And I'm going to need some pictures.And go through those drawers.
至少两人检查监视录像带
And I want at least two people going over the surveillance tapes.
- 这个可以吗?,- 这些是她的衣服?
That work?Are those all her clothes?
她显然还在这楼里
She's obviously still in the building.
她去哪了? 想干什么?
So where did she go?What does she want?
看她男友?
See her boyfriend?
她没带手机
She didn't take her phone.
她想出去
She wants to be outside.
如果你想吓唬家长,你做到了
If you're trying to scare your parents,great job.
可以回去了吗?
Can we go back now?
我恨她
I hate her.
我8岁的时候, 病了
When I was eight years old,I was sick.
不是真的病了, 这不重要,当时我妈--
Not really sick,but the point is,my mom,she--
她一直就这样
she was like this before.
每晚9点回家, 周末不能出去,不能做运动
Home by 9:00 every night.Can't go out on the weekends.Can't do sports.
心移植正中她的下怀
Transplant just gave her what she always wanted.
Melinda...你有心力衰竭
Melinda...you had heart failure.
现在苛责你妈妈对你过分保护
This is kind of an insane time
有点不是时候
to be criticizing your mom about being overprotective.
我知道. 我是说,这就更糟糕了,她所有的这些疯狂,这就...
I know. I mean,this is what makes it even worse.All of her craziness,it just...
让它看起来更加合理了
it makes sense now.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be all right.
我甚至都没有试过到外面去
I didn't even try to get outside.
我太害怕了
I was too scared.
来吧
Come on.
Melinda,请朝着我往回走
Melinda,please walk back towards me.
为什么?
Why?
可以么?
Please?
感觉有点奇怪
It feels kind of weird.
这被称为跨阈步态
It's called steppage gait.
严重么?
is it serious?
不一定
Not necessarily.
好的,把你的腿伸出来,保持住
All right,stick your leg out,hold it up.
她还处在活检的麻醉中,如果考虑到她缺氧的话--
She was under anesthesia for the biopsy.If she lost oxygen--
C.T. 排除了脑损伤
C.T. Ruled out brain damage.
把腿放下吧.放松
Put your leg down.Relax.
为什么她的腿像那样抽搐?
Why is her leg twitching like that?
(肌肉 神经的)自发性收缩
Fasciculation.
严重么?
Is that serious?
这是麻痹,而且还在恶化
It's paralysis,and it's ascending.
她会失去她腿部的功能么?
She's going to lose the use of her legs?
这只是开始
To start with.
情况恶化的很快,她现在几乎不能伸腿了
it's ascending fast.She can hardly extend her leg now.
按照这种速度,大概几天后就会发展到她的肺了
At this rate,it'll be up to her lungs in a matter of days.
看来,过敏性反应,心力衰竭,麻痹.
So,anaphylaxis,heart failure,paralysis.
前两个都不能归因到一起,我想三个都放到一起也不可能了
Couldn't put the first two together.I'm guessing we can't put all three together.
蜱麻痹?
Tick paralysis?
也可以解释过敏性反应,甚至也许--
Could also explain the anaphylaxis,maybe even the--
青霉素过敏对过敏性反应的解释要好的多
penicillin allergy explains the allergic reaction much better.
具体的, 蜱麻痹需要有蜱才行
particularly because tick paralysis is usually accompanied by a tick.
我们做了两个详尽的身体检查,来查找昆虫叮咬
We did two comprehensive physicals looking for insect bites.
我们可以把任何其中两个归因到一起么?
Can we put any two of those together?
不如我们规定一下?
How about we stipulate?
你说肯定有某样东西,把这三种症状联系到一起
You argued that there must be something to connect all three symptoms,
你嘲笑我们没有弄清楚是什么
you mocked us for not figuring it out,
而最后你又让我们单独讨论麻痹
and finally you let us discuss the paralysis on its own because
因为这才是要将她至于死地的
it's what's gonna kill her.
现在,它正在恶化.MRI没显示有问题,排除中风和动脉瘤
Now,it's ascending.Her mris are clean,so rule out stroke or aneurysm.
肌萎缩性侧索硬化?,多发性硬化? 进展太快了
als? Ms? Progression's too quick.
白血病引起的脊椎损伤? 太慢了
Spinal lesion from leukemia? Too slow.
最有可能的是古兰－巴雷综合症
It's most likely guillain-barre.
她在服用免疫抑制剂,可能是肉毒杆菌中毒?
She's immunosuppressed.What about botulism?
不可能,除非最后几天她倒立着走来走去
Not unless she's been walking around on her hands the last couple of days.
肉毒杆菌中毒引起的麻痹症状,是逐渐减轻的 不是恶化的
Botulism paralysis is descending,not ascending.
有可能西尼罗河热,甚至小儿麻痹,考虑到她免疫系统有问题
Could be a virus.West nile,even polio with her immune system shot.
做个腰椎穿刺,做个pcrs来检查病毒
Get an lp and do pcrs for the viruses.
还有做一个肌电图来检查一下,古兰－巴雷综合症
And get an emg to check for guillain-barre.
Foreman说的没错,我们得找出为什么她出现麻痹症状
Foreman's right. We gotta find out why she's paralyzed.
但不是在这之前傻傻盯着我看几秒钟
But not before staring at me dumbly for a few seconds.
我们对你女儿又做了一些测试
we ran more tests on your daughter.
我们做了一个腰椎穿刺,得到了一些脊髓液
We took a lumbar puncture,got some spinal fluid.
然后我们把她带到实验室,寻找是否有受到感染
Then we brought her to the lab to look for infections that
这种感染可能影响到她的大脑
could be affecting her brain.
我们也做了肌电图,检测她的肌肉和神经
We also did an emg to check how her muscles and nerves
如何对电脉冲做出反应
are responding to electrical impulses.
很不幸,她在膝盖以上的肌肉,显示越来越无力
Unfortunately,her muscles are showing increased weakness above the knee.
你是说她的情况变得更糟糕了么?
You mean she's getting worse?
腰椎穿刺和pcrs排除了,小儿麻痹症和西尼罗河热的可能
The lp and pcrs ruled out polio and west nile.
我们认为是古兰－巴雷综合症
We think it's guillain-barre.
身体的免疫响应出了毛病
The body's immune response goes haywire
开始攻击末稍神经
and starts attacking the peripheral nerves.
引起了肌肉无力和麻痹
It causes muscle weakness and paralysis.
情况有多糟糕?
How bad is it?
很严重 但是血浆置换法,通常对古兰－巴雷综合症疗效显著
It's serious,but guillain-barre usually responds very well to plasmapheresis.
你知道,血浆
you see,the plasma,
她血液中的液体部分,包含了大部分的抗体
the clear liquid part of her blood,contains most of the antibodies,
这些抗体反应过度,攻击她的神经系统
which are overreacting and attacking her nervous system.
机器将她的血液在离心机中进行旋转
The machine spins her blood in a centrifuge
基于重量将她的血液各部分分离
and separates parts of the blood based on weight.
白血球是最重的
White blood cells are the heaviest,
然后是红血球,然后是血小板和血浆
then the red cells,then platelets and plasma.
我们丢掉引起问题的部分
We discard the stuff that's causing all the trouble
将有益的血细胞负载在替代液中,返送回她的身体
and return the good blood cells back to her body in a replacement fluid.
如果行的通,几天后我们就会看到结果
If it works,we'll see results in a couple of days.
上星期你没收到,给我的电话留言吧,是不是?
You didn't get any messages for me last week,did you?
没
Nope.
有意思了.那家伙最后打电话来了,我丢掉了那个住处
That's funny.The guy finally called back.The place I lost?
他说他留了三条语音信息
He said he left three voicemails.
要尿尿
Gotta pee.
三条我从来没有收到过的信息,如果说的还不够清楚
Which I never got,if that wasn't clear.
他肯定在扯谎
He must be lying.
你不会想要和一个说谎的人住在一起的
You wouldn't want to live with a liar.
你删了给我的留言?
You erased my messages?
决定了我想要你留下来,跟你说过了，没有么?
Decided I wanted you to stay.Told you that,didn't I?
你...可怜,又孤单一人,而你又要把我困在这里
You're...miserable,and you're lonely,and you're gonna trap me here
让我也完全和你一样可怜孤单
to keep me every bit as miserable and lonely,too.
Yeah,你很快乐, 快乐, 快乐
Yeah,and you're happy,happy,happy.
很明显我正在经历一段艰难的时间
Okay.Hey,I'm obviously going through a rough patch here.
妻子离去,要把某人轰走
Wife leaves,tends to bum somebody out.
你知道我尿到哪里去了么?
Do you know where my pee went?
你没有对准枪口?
You're missing some?
不是.从我里面出来一路流向厕所,那么,怎么会这样?
No. Came out of me and went right into the toilet.Now,why would that be?
你是William Tell(神箭手的名字),你可以从一个人的头上射下苹果?
You're william tell.You could pick an apple off someone's head?
不,是因为厕所里面没有,塑料的包裹布铺在地上
No,it's because there was no clear plastic wrap over the toilet.
厨房里铺的那种东东,你有的是时间，缺的只是决心
Stuff's in the kitchen.You have plenty of time.All that was missing was the will.
这里不是大学宿舍
This isn't a college dorm.
可以是的
It could be.
我们不是18岁了
We're not 18!
那又怎样?
So what?
我对你做了什么?
What did I do to you?
我骗你刷盘子,我让你坐在台阶上
I scammed you into doing the dishes,I made you sit on the steps.
我没有弄死你的小狗
I didn't kill your puppy.
我没有让你陷入痛苦
I did not make you miserable.
哦,说来这还是治疗喽?
Oh,so this is therapy?
不. 只是...能让我笑起来
No. It's just...makes me smile.
好的,我明天就找一个新的地方
All right,I'm finding a new place tomorrow.
好的,但不是今晚
Right,but not tonight.
Well,我想我睡着的时候,你要刮掉我的眉毛
Well,I figure you wanna shave my eyebrows while I'm asleep.
我不会剥夺你最后一次笑的机会
I wouldn't wanna deprive you of that last smile.
你哪里都不会去的
You're not going anywhere.
你会坐在我的沙发上,让我们俩都郁闷
You're gonna sit on my couch,and depress us both,
因为你不敢承认你和你老婆玩完了
because you just can't admit that it's over with your wife.
没错.我是来这里度假的
That's right.I'm here on vacation.
你找过律师了么?
Have you gotten a lawyer yet?
那--那不是...
That's--that's not...
你打过电话给任何一个了么?
you even called one?
只要你在这里,这就只是一场吵架
As long as you're here,it's just a fight.
你一找到一个地方,那么这就是离婚了
As soon as you get a place,then it's a divorce.
什么事都糟透了
Everything sucks.
还是可能找到一些可以让人去笑的东西
Might as well find something to smile about.
反射正在变得更加的微弱
Reflexes are marginally weaker.
麻痹正在变得更加恶化?
The paralysis is getting worse?
有时需要几个疗程让血浆置换法见效
Sometimes it takes a few treatments for the plasmapheresis to work.
为什么这一切一直发生在我身上?
Why do these things keep happening to me?
Dan回来了
Dan's back.
Hey,宝贝,你听到了么?Dan来了
Hey,baby,did you hear that?Dan's here.
我不想见他
I don't want to see him.
我会告诉他等下再过来
I'll tell him to come back later.
不.妈妈,留在这里,求你
No.Mommy,stay here,please.
当然
Of course.
她还好吧?
Is she okay?
她在睡觉
She's sleeping.
我肯定她很疲惫了
I'm sure she's exhausted.
抗排异药物引起情绪不稳定很常见
Mood swings are common with the anti-rejection meds.
不. 她有过情绪不稳定,不是这个 这是--
No. She's had mood swings.This isn't it. This is--
她已经放弃了
she's given up.
我知道你认为我--
I know you think I'm--
这不是我想要的
this isn't what I wanted.
她总是和我争吵
She's always fought with me.
从她是一个婴孩开始,她就这么的顽固
Ever since she was a baby,she was so damn stubborn.
但是我从未想要她这样子
But I never wanted her like this.
我只想要她平平安安
I just wanted her safe.
医生! 医生!
Doctor! Doctor!
她不能呼吸了!
She can't breathe!
她不能说完一整句话
She couldn't get a whole sentence out.
她正在使用附肌呼吸
She's using accessory muscles.
血氧量降到90.肺部没有问题么?,你有没有感觉到舌头吞进去?
02 sat's down to 90.Lungs clear?Does your tongue feel swollen?
痒么?没有麻疹
Is it itchy? No hives.
不是过敏.嘴唇发紫.我们得做插管了
It's not an allergy.Lips are cyanotic.We got to intubate.
你们在做什么?
What are you doing?
注入劳拉西泮
Pushing lorazepam.
她得不到足够的氧气.我们得帮助她呼吸
She's not getting enough oxygen.We've got to assist her breathing.
这是怎么回事?是对治疗的反应么?
What was that?Was that a reaction to the treatment?
是麻痹.已经蔓延到她的肺部.
It's the paralysis.It's reaching her lungs.
melinda就要死了.
melinda's dying.
我们都快死了.多快?
We're all dying.How fast?
对于兰德里－古兰－巴雷综合症来说太快了
Too fast for guillain-barre.
Cuddy 要给她做一个MRI排除脊椎损伤的可能
Cuddy wants to get her an mri to rule out a spinal lesion.
Cuddy? 她管这个干什么?
Cuddy? What's she doing on this?
她的家人对我们失去了信任
The family lost confidence in us.
我不怪他们.我马上赶来
I don't blame them.I'll be right in.
可能是她中了神经毒剂
It's like she got poisoned with a nerve agent.
黏着性吸入.可以解释她为什么没有承认
Glue inhalation. Would explain why she hasn't admitted it.
毒物甄别显示没有大麻
Tox screen was clear for pot.
中产阶级的心脏移植病人吸毒?
Middle-class heart transplant patient's gonna huff glue?
杀虫剂?
Pesticides?
一年的这个时候,他们没有在喷药
this time of year,they're not spraying.
这个女孩很倔.她得到她想要的
This girl's tough.She gets what she wants.
她被剥夺了和人接触的机会,她就会给自己找一个秘密的情人
She's deprived of human contact,she gets herself a backdoor man.
或者说对于她的情况,一个爬边窗进来的男孩
Or in her case,a side window boy.
她还被夺去了什么?
What else has she been deprived of?
因为心脏病她按规定饮食
She's on a special diet because of the cardiology
男朋友带给她热腾的牛肉
the boyfriend brings the hot beef.
他还带来了副菜:肉毒杆菌.
He also brings a side dish:Botulism.
麻痹正在恶化,记得么?
This is paralysis is ascending,remember?
如果她心脏的问题是她麻痹的真正原因,就不是这样了
Not if the heart problem's really a paralytic problem.
她为什么会承认性而不是食物?
Why would she admit the sex and not the food?
她什么都没有承认
She didn't admit anything.
他承认了有过,,而我们没有问他有关食物的事情
He admitted the sex,andwe didn't ask him about food.
给我一只老鼠
get me a rat.
你有一只老鼠了
You have a rat.
什么?我不会杀了Steve的,(以前从Stacy家抓到的一只)
What?I'm not gonna kill steve.
唯一确认此事的方法是...
Only way to confirm this...
给这只老鼠注射进她的血液,并等它的肉毒杆菌发展到危及生命的地步
inject the rat with her blood and wait for it to get all botulistic on your ass.
同时,我要到楼下去吓唬一个被吓坏的
In the meantime,I'm going downstairs to browbeat a scared,
快要死去的十几岁的女孩直到她
dying teenage girl until she...
像一个被吓坏的快要死去的,十几岁的女孩一样崩溃
breaks down like a scared,dying teenage girl.
你起的很早嘛
You're up early.
Cuddy需要一些建议
Cuddy needed a consult.
我们正在检验白血病引起的脊椎损伤
We're checking for spinal lesions from leukemia.
我知道.很符合情况
I know.Fits perfectly.
除非这是一个有过敏性反应，心力衰竭,以及麻痹症状的病人
Unless this is the patient with the anaphylaxis,the heart failure,
这种情况下,你在浪费你的时间
and the paralysis,in which case,you're wasting your time.
我们需要来自第二方的建议
We wanted a second opinion.
第二方?我们肯定至少折磨过你8次了
Second? We must have gin you at least eight.
Okay,well这是第9次
Okay,well here's nine.
肉毒杆菌
Botulism.
听我说. 你有没有吃过不正常的东西?,任何罐装食品?
Listen to me. Have you eaten anything abnormal?Any canned foods?
没有
No.
你肯定?
You sure?
对你的父母撒谎通常是对的
Lying to your parents is usually the right thing to do,
但是濒临死亡时可是例外
but there is an impending death exception.
别这么和她说话
Don't talk to her like that.
你是对的. 她从不说谎.我太粗鲁了
You're right. She never lies.I was being rude.
当你的男朋友周五晚上偷摸进来,惊喜吧
When your boyfriend snuck in on friday night--surprise--
也许他给了你一点性作为治疗,huh?
perhaps he got you some sexy little treats,huh?
一些“蜜”或者一些可以吃的内,衣裤,一些按摩油
Some honey or some edible underwear,some massage oils.
得了,什么都好
Come on,anything.
我们没有--
We didn't--
我们都了解性的
we know about the sex.
结果是danny的小danny上都是青霉素
Turns out that danny's little danny is full of penicillin.
这是导致你过敏性休克的原因
That's what caused your anaphylactic shock.
你没有告诉我们是这个--
You didn't tell us that's what--
不. 是--他服用了氯洁霉素,是我在用的
no. It was--he took clindamycin.What I use.
他说他正在服用青霉素
He said he was on penicillin.
我看到瓶子了
I saw the bottle.
这是非青霉素类的抗生素
It's a non-penicillin antibiotic.
如果抗生素没有引起过敏性反应的话
If the antibiotics didn't cause the anaphylaxis...
问题还在
it's still on the table.
一切都关联起来了
Everything is connected.
我们在讨论什么?有什么区别么?
What did we discuss?What was the differential?
Cameron说过...
Cameron said...
当dan那天晚上到你房子里,他有穿过一片高草么?
when dan came to your house that night,did he go through any tall grass?
爬过一片篱笆
Climbed a fence.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
周五晚上你的女儿有两位访客
Your daughter had two visitors on friday night.
其中之一还在这个屋子里面
One of them is still in the room.
她有壁虱性麻痹
She has tick paralysis.
Dan在他的牛仔裤上带上了扁虱
Dan tracked a tick onto his jeans,
这本不会是一个问题,但是作为一个年轻人
which wouldn't be a problem.But being a teenager,
dan不能把他的扁虱保留在他的裤子上
dan couldn't keep his tick in his pants.
我们已经检查过她了
we already checked her.
现在我在检查她
Now I'm checking her.
蜱叮咬通常不会引起过敏性休克
Tick bites don't ordinarily cause anaphylactic shock.
这个女孩的过敏性是不同寻常的
This girl's allergies are not ordinary.
House,出去.我们要重新给,她插管,给她做MRI
House,get out of here.We have to re-intubate her,get her into the mri.
时间过程再符合不过了
The time course is perfect.
叮咬本身引发了过敏反应
The bite itself sets off an allergic reaction.
毒素花了四天发生作用,脆弱的心脏, 第一个中镖
Venom takes four days to kick in,heart's vulnerable, hits that first,
而一天以后引发了不断恶化的麻痹
and a day later sets off the ascending paralysis.
除了蜱通常不是看不到的
Except that ticks aren't usually invisible.
它们是不显眼的直到你找到它们
They are until you find them.
哦不,那是头皮屑.,那一点也不像我原来希望的那样有戏剧性
Oh no,that's dandruff.That wasn't nearly as dramatic as I'd hoped.
只是意味着下次情况会更好
Just means the next time it'll be even better.
发生什么了?
What's happening?
那是蜱的毒素让情况恶化了
That's the tick venom ascending.
或者是这种情况或者你让她心力衰竭了,血压在降低.心率,47.
Either that or you stressed her into heart failure.Bp's dropping.Heart rate,47.
我在注入阿托品
I'm administering atropine.
她需要一次静脉导管了
She's going to need a transvenous pacing wire.
Okay,魔术师的搜寻结束了,现在是真材实料的医生的时间
Okay,magical tick hunt is over.Only real doctor stuff now.
这只会变得更加糟糕
This is just gonna get worse.
蜱得到养分的时间越久,它产生的毒素就越多
Ticks produce more toxins the longer they feed.
她一个小时以后就会死了,即使你往她的心脏加满喷气机燃料
She's gonna be dead in an hour even if you pump her heart full of jet fuel,
除非你们让我找到蜱
unless you let me find the tick.
他会是对的么?
Could he be right?
我唯一确定的是你女儿的心脏
The only thing I know for sure is that your daughter's heart
不会再挺过20分钟如果得不到治疗的话
won't last another 20 minutes without treatment.
Okay,我只需要一个最后的建议
Okay,I just need one final instruction.
当我尸检的时候发现蜱,你还要不要知道?
When I find the tick on the autopsy,do you want to know?
不要知道 可能让你们,心理上的处理更容易一些
I'm thinking not.Probably make the coping easier.
不要再跟他们说话了!
Stop talking to them!
呼心脏病科的borsisky,让她的小组到这里
Page borsisky in cardiology.Get her team down here stat.
让他们出去.也把House弄出去
Get them out of here.Get house out of here,too.
Wilson医生,我可能用的上你的帮忙
Dr. Wilson,I could use your help.
Well,我不知道多巴胺是否足够
Well,I don't know if the dopamine's enough.
--她也许需要乳酸氨力农,--为什么? 那是什么?
--She may need inamrinone lactate. --Why? What's that?
她不需要--她也许需要更强的血管收缩剂
She doesn't--she might need stronger pressors.
而放射科一点这个都没有
They don't have any in radiology.
乳酸氨力农可能引起,心律不齐与血小板减少
Inamrinone can cause arrhythmia and thrombocytopenia.
不用乳酸氨力农可能导致死亡,死亡更糟糕
Not inamrinone could cause death.Death's worse.
我们需要把她弄到重点护理病房
We have to get her up to the icu.
抱歉.这里有点挤
Sorry.Little crowded here.
House,从电梯里面出来
House,get out of the elevator.
很欢迎你们等下一部
You're welcome to wait for the next one.
你护的住她吧?护的住
You got her?Got her.
Well,只要我们被困在这里
Well,as long as we're stuck here,
就会是一个找蜱的好机会
this might be a good time to look for that tick.
把电梯重新开动
Turn the elevator back on.
就等一会儿,亲爱的
Just be a minute,honey.
阿托品的效果在减弱
Atropine's wearing off.
那就再注射
So inject her again.
那只是暂时有效
That's just temporary.
暂时就够了,我们又不是在贴墙纸
Temporary's fine.We're not hanging wallpaper.
我们得把她送到楼上给她使用去甲肾上腺素
We've got to get her upstairs and put her on norepinephrine.
这不是青霉素的问题
It wasn't penicillin.
你还认为症状之间没有关联?
You still think the symptoms are unconnected?
我们得先搞定她的心脏
We've got to take care of her heart before--
你早上醒来,你的漆料都已剥落,门帘也不见了
you wake up in the morning,your paint's peeling,your curtains are gone,
还有水也开了,你先处理哪个问题?
and the water's boiling.Which problem do you deal with first?
什么都不是!大楼已经着火了!
House--none of them!The building's on fire!
我们对症治疗,她死定了,我们找出病因,她会活下来
We treat her symptoms,she dies.We find the cause,she lives.
蜱一直往静脉里面注入毒素,我们除掉它,她就会没事的
That tick is an I.V. Drip of poison.We unhook it,she'll be fine.
这是我最后一支阿托品
It's my last atropine.
可以给我们大约三分钟
Last us about three minutes.
我们把她的袍子翻开
Let's get her gown up.
她的心率降到35以下,我们就把她送到重点护理病房
Her heart rate falls below 35,we're getting her to the icu.
我不会让她死在电梯里面的
I'm not gonna let her die in this elevator.
他们在哪里?
Where are they?
让设备维护小组马上到这里来
Get maintenance up here right away.
--耳道没有问题. --左腿没有问题
--Ear canal's clean. --Left foot's clean.
如果它不在这里,我们只有在--
If it's not here,we've only got--
心率46.
Heart rate's 46.
在这里.就像一颗痣或者一个斑点,有时被我们漏过了
It's here.Looks like a mole or a freckle.Something we missed.
检查腋窝
Check the armpits.
Foreman是一个很出色的医生,他能够处理这个状况
Dr di blane .is a excellent doctor.He's able to handle it.
你知道我对这个经历感觉怎样?
You know how i feel the experience?
你有很多病人在电梯里面死掉?
you lose a lot of patients on elevators?
维护人员说电梯不是自己停下来的
The maintenance guy said it didn't just stop on its own,
而是他们按下了紧急停止的按钮
that they hit the emergency stop button.
Well,我肯定我们是弄错了
Well,I'm sure us mistaken.
会阴.我们检查过了
Perineum.We checked it.
如果我们把她送到楼上--, --上颌.检查过了
If we get her upstairs-- --maxilla.Checked.
降到38了
Down to 38.
我们没有太多的时间了
We don't have a lot of time.
眉毛,耳鼓,阴毛
Eyebrows,eardrums,pubic hair.
检查了,检查了,检查了
Checked,checked,checked.
我们什么地方都检查过了!没有--
We checked everywhere!It's not--
35. 我们得把她送到重点看护病房了
35. We got to get her to the icu.
我们还没有找到蜱
we haven't found the tick yet.
我们已经是绑架了她!,你还要加上谋杀么
We already kidnapped her!You want to add murder?
我们已经检查过她皮肤和身体,的几乎每一寸地方,house!
We've looked over every inch of skin on her body,house!
结束了
It's over.
这是你第一次的性经历?
is that the first time you had sex?
还有其他的东西在那里,她可能还没有意识到
With all the other stuff going on down there,she might not have realized.
你恶心,可悲--
You sick,miserable--
你在干什么? 哦,我的天!
what are you doing? Oh,my god!
看见了?早告诉你会更有戏剧性
See? Told you it'd be even more dramatic.
注入去甲肾上腺素,让她的心脏恢复正常
Push norepinephrine.Get her heart back to normal.
到明天她就会被完全的治愈
She'll be completely cured by tomorrow.
Foreman,我们把她送到重点看护病房
Foreman,let's get her into the icu.
乳酸氨力农是一个愚蠢的主意
Inamrinone was a stupid idea,
除非你是想要我在电梯里面,搞定这女孩的问题
unless you wanted me to get that girl on the elevator.
哦,我不会那么做的
Oh,I wouldn't do that.
如果你做了,不会尊重你的
Wouldn't respect you if you did.
看起来像有人在你睡觉的时候,把你的拐杖从中间锉了一半
Looks like somebody filed halfway through your cane while you were sleeping.
反射恢复正常了,心脏看来也好起来了
Reflexes back to normal.Heart's looking good,too.
我会叫护士进来,我们会把你转出特别看护病房
I'll send in the nurse,we'll get you transferred out of icu,
早上你就可以出院了
you'll be discharged in the morning.
谢谢上帝.我只想要回家
Thank god.I just want to get home.
还有周一就回到学校
And back to school on monday.
我还没准备好
I'm not ready.
你已经准备好了
You're ready.
我还在生病 妈妈
I'm sick,mom.
你没有生病
You're not sick.
你要去上学了,你会见到你的朋友还有你的男朋友
You're gonna go to class,and you're gonna see your friends and your boyfriend.
今天我打电话给一个离婚律师了
I called a divorce lawyer today.
这是说你要走了?
Does that mean you're leaving?
差不多吧
At some point.
你可能不想就正好坐在那里
You might not want to sit exactly there.